<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Team 8 App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="youtube_video_id">d9ZrzAQRyg8</string>

    <string name="menu_title">Menu</string>

    <!-- Landing page strings -->
    <string name="newcastle_logo">Newcastle University Logo</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="open_day_button">Open Day</string>
    <string name="post_app_day_button">Post Application Visit Day</string>

    <!-- FAQ strings -->
    <string name="faqTitle">Frequently Asked Questions</string>

    <string name="question1">Is there disabled access to the building?</string>
    <string name="answer1">Yes, the entrances are wheelchair accessible and there is lift access to the first four floors of the building.</string>

    <string name="question2">Where are the medical centers located near the USB?</string>
    <string name="answer2">There are first aid trained staff on premises to assist in medical needs as well as Newcastle Hospital close by if further medical help is required.</string>

    <string name="question3">Is food available within the USB?</string>
    <string name="answer3">There is food available within the building\'s cafeteria on the ground floor.</string>

    <string name="question4">What nearby transport links are available?</string>
    <string name="answer4">The closest bus and metro stations to the USB are just outside St. James\' Park, with the bus station on Barrack Road and a metro stop at the football grounds. The USB is also located just a 10 minute walk from the train station.</string>

    <string name="question5">Where are toilets located?</string>
    <string name="answer5">Toilets are located on every floor in the building, disabled toilets are available on all floors with disabled access.</string>

    <!-- Open Day Strings -->
    <string name="open_Day_Info">The open days here at Newcastle are a great way to explore and experience the Newcastle university campus directly.
        During Summer and Autumn annually the university hosts the open days for students interested in seeking a higher education after school.\n\n
        On the day you’ll be provided with a number of activities and aimed to help you learn more about the USB,
        the university in general, and get a feel for life in the city.
        You’ll also be given the chance to get face to face with a number of teachers, staff, and students currently studying at the university.\n
    </string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="open_day">Open Day</string>
    <string name="menu_button">Menu Button</string>
    <string name="open_day_video">Open day video</string>

    <!--Post Applicant Day Strings -->
    <string name="post_app_title">Post Applicant Days</string>
    <string name="post_app_text_p1">This Offer Holder Day will provide you with the opportunity to put questions to current staff and students,
        visit teaching and research labs and see examples of student work. Questions can range from the course, to University life,
        feel free to ask anything!
        \n\nAs a prospective student you will get another look at the University and the environment you will be working in.
        Additionally it will give the opportunity to revisit the USB.
        This is where you will be spending most of your time when working at Newcastle for this course.
    </string>
    <string name = "post_app_header">
        What will happen on the day?
    </string>
    <string name = "post_app_header2">
        The day will take place from 10:00 to 15:30 and include:
    </string>

    <string name="post_app_text_p2">
    - Registration and refreshments in the USB \n
    - Welcome from the Head of School\n
    - Icebreaker session for applicants\n
    - Buffet lunch for all\n
    - Student led talks on life as a student in Newcastle\n
    - Demonstrations and talks by our research groups\n
    - Alumni talk\n
    - Informal chat with an academic\n
    - Chats with existing students and academic staff over coffee and cake\n
    - Tours of the School’s facilities
    </string>


    <!--Tours Strings -->
    <string name="preset_tour">Take a tour!</string>
    <string name="open_floor_plan">View Floor Plan</string>
    <string name="floor_plan_picture">Picture of the Floor Plan</string>
    <string name="floor_info">Information relative to the floor being currently viewed</string>
    <string name="next_step">Next Step</string>
    <string name="playbtn">Play Video</string>

    <!-- Self guided tour menu -->
    <string name="self_guided_title">Self Guided Tour</string>
    <string name="preset_tour_button">Follow a pre-set walking tour</string>
    <string name="own_pace_button">Discover at your own pace</string>

    <!--Text For Pre-Config Tour-->

    <!-- Titles -->
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="buildings_title">Surrounding Buildings</string>
    <string name="design_title">Design of the USB</string>
    <string name="history_title">History of the School</string>
    <string name="atrium_title">The Atrium</string>
    <string name="openlab_title">Open Lab / Lectures</string>
    <string name="staff_title">TIG / Staff</string>
    <string name="flatfloor_title">Flat Floor Teaching</string>
    <string name="terrace_title">The Terrace</string>
    <string name="research_title">Research Groups</string>

    <!-- Images -->
    <string name="decision_room_image">Image of the decision theatre</string>
    <string name="eat_urban_image">Image of the cafeteria within the USB</string>
    <string name="fredrick_douglass_image">Image of the fredrick douglass building</string>
    <string name="nida_building_image">Image of the National Innovation Center for Data and Ageing</string>
    <string name="biosphere_image">Image of the biosphere</string>
    <string name="usb_windows_image">Image of the USB from outside focusing on the buildings windows</string>
    <string name="flat_floor_image">Image of the flat floor teaching area within the USB</string>
    <string name="usb_reception_image">Image of the ground floor reception</string>
    <string name="open_lab_image">Image of one of the open labs in the USB</string>
    <string name="lecture_theatre_image">Image of the lecture theatre</string>
    <string name="research_group_image">Image of research being done by one of the research groups within the building</string>
    <string name="school_reception_image">Image of the 2nd floor computer science school reception</string>
    <string name="terrace_image">Image of the terrace</string>

    <!-- Content -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the award winning Urban Sciences Building (also known as USB)
        – home of the School of Computing based on the Newcastle Helix site.\n\n\n
        This is part of a £350 million flagship city centre regeneration project bringing together
        academia, the public sector, communities, business and industry.\n\n\n
        The 24 acre site is being developed with Newcastle City Council and Legal and General.
        \n\n\n
        It is planned to be a mixture of residential and academic units and commercial businesses
        on the site. \n\n\n
        The site was originally the home to Scottish and Newcastle breweries who brewed Newcastle Brown
        Ale which is now brewed in the Netherlands .
    </string>

    <string name="helix">You may think we are working and studying on a building site, but the "Helix" is
        an exciting new development with buildings either side of us providing lecture space and
        big data opportunities for our students.</string>
    <string name="frederick_douglass_title">The Frederick Douglass Centre</string>
    <string name="frederick_douglass">Designed to offer multi-use space for outreach and teaching events, it houses an auditorium
        that can hold 750 people, and can hold 200 more in a collaborative lecture theatre.</string>
    <string name="NIC_title">The National Innovation Centre for Data and Ageing</string>
        <string name="NIC">This building houses 2 research centres intended to enable businesses to work closely with
        researchers in order to develop new technology around the use of data and helping society
        to deal with the consequences of ageing.</string>
    <string name="biosphere_title">The Biosphere</string>
    <string name="biosphere">This is a unique eco-system of commercial laboratory space, offices and support services,
        leading the way as a home for ambitious companies within life sciences, healthcare and
        emerging fields of biotechnology.</string>

    <string name="design_1">The design of the building has had a lot of input from
        academics which has lead to some good design features that would have otherwise not been
        included.</string>
    <string name="windows">The USB\'s Windows</string>
    <string name="design_2">
        It combines all parts of the School of Computing from 3 buildings into 1.\n\n
        It features Big Data Windows, the dots and lines across the windows at the front of the
        building represent a self portrait of the University website, with the lines, dots and
        circles representing the information and resources.\n\nThe building also features elements of
        the past in its design, with the outside being covered in patterns of dots. These represent
        the punch cards that were used to control the machines in the 19th centre and were used last
        carrying data and instructions for calculating machines.
    </string>

    <string name="history">Although housed in a new state of the art building, the school offers a
        long history having recently celebrated its 60th birthday and is one of the oldest schools
        of computer science in the UK and was one of the first to award both undergraduate and
        postgraduate degrees. In 2019 we celebrate 50 years since the first graduation from an
        undergraduate programme.\n\n
       The display next to reception shows some of our oldest computers and those we have used
        throughout our 60 year history.
    </string>
    <string name="reception">The Building Reception</string>

    <string name="ground_floor_sub_title">Ground Floor Facilities</string>
    <string name="ground_floor">
        There is the Cyber Physical Systems Laboratory, This lab focuses on systems that combine
        hardware, software, networking and control. It is developing integrated systems for
        transport, smart grids, building infrastructure etc.\n\n
        There is the Decision Theatre, this
        is an iInteractive 3D facility linked to the Urban Observatory that provides companies,
        policy makers and researchers with powerful data visualisation for collaborative decision
        making.\n\n
        Finally there is the Urban Observatory, this is the largest urban sensing network
        in the UK.  It records millions of observations daily and provides insights into how
        Newcastle works over multiple time frames and sectors.
    </string>
    <string name="cafe_sub_title">Eat @ Urban</string>
    <string name="cafe">
        The perfect space to refuel, whether it’s a formal meeting or a relaxing
        break, with a choice of barista coffee, deli sandwiches, paninis, jacket potatoes and
        snacks. This is open to staff, students and the general public and is open 8-4 on a daily
        basis in term time.
    </string>

    <string name="open_lab">Open lab is focused on human interaction with computers and human based
        design of computer systems.\n\n
        One of the examples of projects in the Open Lab is the ambient kitchen. This has utensils
        that contain instruments that communicate with the network around them allowing the kitchen
        to help you work out if you are stirring, cutting, how long you have been doing it for etc.
        This technology might allow someone with mild dementia to get help in the kitchen and enable
        them to get computer aided assistance.
    </string>
    <string name="lecture_theatre">The lecture theatre has a capacity of 303 students and has the
        ability for the lecturer to customise what is shown on each of the projected screen.
        This means the lecture can still display the lecture notes whilst they are demonstrating a
        piece of code or practical element of the lecture.\n\n
        Each seat has lumbar support and access to a power socket with USB ports.
    </string>

    <string name="school_reception">
        On the second floor you can find the exit to the lecture theatre, the School reception and our teaching innovation group.\n\n
        The School Office contains all the Professional Services staff and the NUIT Computing
        Support team.\n\n
        This is the area where you should come and ask for help and support when required.
    </string>
    <string name="teaching_inov_group">
        The Teaching Innovation Group aim to encourage, foster and pursue innovation in teaching.
        TIG run our Outreach programme with the Computing at School initiative.\n\n\ This programme runs
        teacher training, outreach events and visits to schools.\n\n TIG are also responsible for
        reviewing existing degree programmes, developing employability skills and maintaining links
        with industry.
    </string>

    <string name="flat_floor_teaching1">The flat floor teaching spaces have 312 machines, with all
        the software that students will need for their degree.\n\n The machines run NetSupport software
        that allows the lecturer to send and receive files from the class. The lecturer is also able
        to share their screen to the students and give a lecture.</string>
    <string name="flat_floor_teaching2">
        The desks allow students to work on their own laptop or use pen and paper for the
        modules that do not require a computer.\n\n The undergraduate and the MSc Computer Science
        students use this area.
    </string>

    <string name="fourth_floor">On the fourth floor, there is more flat floor teaching spaces and
        seminar rooms but these are usually used by 3rd year students and above.</string>
    <string name="roof_terrace">
        The building has 2 roof terraces on the 4th and 5th floors, with the one on the 4th floor
        accessible to students.\n\n This roof terrace has a wild flower meadow which is great for bees
        and the views over Newcastle.
    </string>

    <string name="research_groups1">The 5th and 6th floors of the building are home to 2 research
        groups.\n\n
        Interdisciplinary Computing and Complex BioSystems have expertise in machine intelligence,
        complex systems and computational biology. The problems they focus on are in natural complex
        systems and synthetic ones. This ranges from biology, chemistry and physics, to biological
        engineering, health care, and software engineering.
    </string>
    <string name="research_groups2">
        Secure and Resilient Systems, Their research directly contributes to creating modern
        information systems, networks and infrastructures.\n\n They are dependable and secure in all
        aspects. The Secure and Resilient Systems group investigates fundamental concepts,
        development techniques, models, architectures and mechanisms that directly contribute to
        creating modern information systems, networks and infrastructures that are dependable and
        secure in all aspects.
    </string>

    <string name="end_tour">We hope you enjoyed this brief tour of our building!</string>

    <!-- Discover at own pace menu -->
    <string name="floor1_button">1st Floor</string>
    <string name="floor2_button">2nd Floor</string>
    <string name="floor3_button">3rd Floor</string>
    <string name="floor4_button">4th Floor</string>
    <string name="floor5_button">5th Floor</string>
    <string name="floor6_button">6th Floor</string>

    <!-- Self guided tour strings -->
    <string name="error_message">Error loading floor</string>
    <string name="floor1_image_desc">floor plan of floor one</string>
    <string name="floor2_image_desc">floor plan of floor two</string>
    <string name="floor3_image_desc">floor plan of floor three</string>
    <string name="floor4_image_desc">floor plan of floor four</string>
    <string name="floor5_image_desc">floor plan of floor five</string>
    <string name="floor6_image_desc">floor plan of floor six</string>

    <!-- Google Maps Directions Strings -->
    <string name="directions_title">Directions to the USB</string>
    <string name="directions_from_main_campus">Directions from Main Campus</string>
    <string name="directions_from_haymarket">Directions from Haymarket</string>
    <string name="directions_from_central_station">Directions from Central Station</string>
    <string name="directions_from_eldon_square">Directions from Eldon Square</string>

    <string name="main_campus_text">Main Campus</string>
    <string name="haymarket_text">Haymarket</string>
    <string name="central_station_text">Central Station</string>
    <string name="eldon_square_text">Eldon Square</string>

    <string name="food_and_drink_stops">Food and Drink</string>
    <string name="university_stops">University</string>
    <string name="accomodation_stops">Accommodation</string>

    <array name="pre_config_tour"></array>

    <!-- Nav Bar Strings -->
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

</resources>
